# Aishat Agunbiade

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Github - https://github.com/YeeshaDev

Email - aishaagunbiade05@gmail.com

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/aisha-agunbiade-88646b1a6/

### **SUMMARY**

A Web Developer specializing in front end development who is fluent in English. Experienced with different stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects and passion for responsive website design using Frontend technologies. I am intrested in joining a team where i can continue my personal growth while working to deliver accessible and efficient user-focused products.

# **SKILL HIGHLIGHTS**

#### **LANGUAGES**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- SQL
- Typescript

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

- React.js
- NextJSTailwind
- Bootstrap

#### **TOOLS**

- Git & Github
- Firebase
- React-Redux
- Figma
- PostMan
- Shadcdn

## **EXPERIENCE**

Lead Frontend Developer - 01/2023 to 02/2024

FLIPTOTECH, Lagos state.

- Led Frontend development initiatives, leveraging Typescript, React and Tailwind to construct responsive, semantic websites with efficient, clean code.
- Directed a small team in developing a user friendly websites for students, ensuring a cohesive project execution and adherence to bet practices

# Web Developer Intern- 01/2022 to 06/2022

AMANDA-AI TECHNOLOGIES, Ikeja, Lagos.

- Collaborated with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. Developed project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Worked with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients
- Debugged and carried out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

# **Research Assistant**- 03/2021 to 03/2022

STRATEGIC BUSINESS TECHSPACE, Anthony, Lagos.

- Reviewed and sorted emails to distribute or initiate responses to inquires
- Evaluated work procedures, schedules and workflow to recommend policies and procedural updates
- Maintained calendar of meetings and events to track and organize activities.

## **FAVORITE PERSONAL PROJECTS**

• **Project website** - This is my personal website which contains all my favorite projects. **Link**: <a href="https://yeeshadev-portfolio.vercel.app/">https://yeeshadev-portfolio.vercel.app/</a> **code**: <a href="https://github.com/YeeshaDev/portfolio">https://github.com/YeeshaDev/portfolio</a>

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

- FreeCampCode JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Jan 2023.
- ALX Software Engineering 04/2022 to 04/2023.